The thing I love most
about Valentine's Day
is the expectation
of the unexpected,
that something
magical could happen
and maybe that special someone
will come back into your life
and change its course
for the better.
Hey, Milwaukee,
Valentine's Day is here,
and we're spreading the love,
right here on WTMC 95.9.
Whether you're planning
a romantic night out
or want to show someone
how much they mean to you,
we've got you covered.
Keep it locked on WTMC 95.9.
♪ My friends say I
should live a little ♪
♪ Need to start
saying yes more ♪
♪ I compromise and meet
'em in the middle ♪
♪ 'Cause new actions will
get you new results ♪
♪ They gave me something
to think about ♪
♪ It's life and I'm
supposed to live it out ♪
Good morning.
♪ I'm holding on
to the universe ♪
♪ Praying that she
don't let me down ♪
♪ I'm afraid ♪
♪ If I try something
crazy, I'm-a end up ♪
♪ In love, love, love ♪
♪ 'Cause the world that
we live in is crazy... ♪
- Good morning!
- Hi, Marvin!
♪ I'm feeling alive ♪
♪ I'm feeling alive,
alive, alive ♪
♪ I'm feeling alive... ♪
- Good morning!
- Good to see you, Marv!
♪ If you feeling what
I'm saying, say ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh-oh-oh... ♪
- Hi!
- Hey, Marvin!
♪ If you feeling what
I'm saying, say ♪
- ♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh-oh-oh ♪
- ♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh-oh-oh ♪
♪ Don't be afraid to go
and try something crazy ♪
♪ You might end up
in love, love, love ♪
♪ 'Cause the world that
we live in is crazy ♪
♪ And we got to learn
to trust, trust, trust ♪
♪ I'm feeling alive,
I'm feeling alive... ♪
♪ I'm feeling alive ♪
♪ I'm feeling alive,
alive, alive ♪
♪ If you feeling what
I'm saying, say ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh-oh-oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh-oh-oh ♪
♪ If you feeling what
I'm saying, say ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ Oh-oh-oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ If you feeling what
I'm saying, say ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh-oh-oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh-oh-oh ♪
♪ If you feeling what
I'm saying, say ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh-oh-oh,
oh, oh, oh... ♪
What the fudge?
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh-oh-oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh-oh-oh ♪
♪ If you feeling what
I'm saying, say ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh-oh-oh... ♪
Zaks.
♪ If you feeling what
I'm saying, say... ♪
Frontier Realty. I
want a home for you.
Ash, it's Marv.
I just got to the
Emerald Springs house.
Someone drew a Hitler
mustache on my yard sign.
Hitler!
- Can you believe that?
- Have some dignity.
It's got to be Jeff Zaks at
Peak Point messing with me.
I have half a mind
to go over there...
And do what, Marv?
Cook him dinner?
The guy has, like, a black belt.
He could crush you
with his thumb.
Eh.
Anything going on at the office?
Only the office
Valentine's Day party.
If one streamer
falls on my desk,
I will stuff it so
far up your asshole
you will be shitting hearts.
I will murder you.
Wow. Someone's in a good mood.
I really... I don't think I
can do this anymore, Marv.
- Do what anymore?
- All of it, you know?
Work. Live.
It's so fucking bleak.
You know, and I
feel, I feel sick.
You're not sick, Ash.
You're depressed.
I get it.
It's very natural to feel
lonely on Valentine's Day.
Look.
Every day is an opportunity
to change your life.
If you're not happy,
do something about it.
I really don't need
a bumper sticker right
now, Marv, please.
I'm serious.
You've got a chef's kitchen,
top-of-the-line appliances,
a beautiful space for those
big family breakfasts.
You know, I remember the
feeling when I bought my home.
It was like, for the
first time in my life,
something was truly all mine.
There's a freedom
in that, you know?
Even if it's just
a little taste.
You want to know my
favorite part about my job?
I get to relive that experience,
that first feeling of
freedom, again and again,
through good folks
like yourselves.
It's why I want a home for you.
It's simple.
I pour everything into it
because it's meaningful.
And because it's
meaningful, I have meaning.
If you find something
you love, go after it.
What do you love, Marv?
The job, of course.
Oh, God, that's sad.
- Cookie?
- No.
Ash, I'm your boss, which
means you have to listen to me.
Hey, Deborah, cookie?
Oh, I'd love a
cookie. Thanks, Marv.
- Toby, hey! Great to see you.
- Hey.
- Cookie?
- Ah, cookie alert.
Hi, Jenny.
-JENNY: Thanks, Marv. These are delicious.
Okay, speaking about bosses,
Cliff came by looking
for you earlier.
Yeah? He say why?
No, he's in a meeting.
Back in a while.
- Hi. Good morning. Cookie?
- Cookies again? Thank you, Marv.
Well, uh, so the Reebers called
about the Emerald Springs house.
They're such freaks.
But they want to
take a look at it.
Great. Schedule it.
After today's open house,
I think it's gonna be competitive.
-Yeah.
Looks like someone's
got a secret admirer.
Who's it from?
Marv, you all right?
Uh...
Not feeling great
all of a sudden.
- Um...
- I-I just need a minute.
Yeah.
Don't forget the office party.
"The animal breathes again.
"And for once, I'm
glad to see these bars.
"These bars that
keep me from myself.
"That keep me from you.
"I pass you rocks,
you tip the scales.
You grind me salt,
I cut your nails."
Raven?
What did you think
of that last stanza?
What?
The last stanza.
Was the imagery too obtuse?
I-I think you can do better.
Your brother Knuckles
wants to know
why Rose is spreading
love on Valentine's Day.
He wants to see her.
Where is she?
I have no idea.
I'm told you watched her
draw her last breath.
And yet...
she breathes again.
I told you, I don't know.
Your coworkers don't know
who you really are, do they?
And I'm willing to keep
your dirty little secret
if you tell me exactly
what I want to know.
Where is Rose?
I know you have, um, too.
And it's not just the cinnamon
hearts I've been eating either.
You're a little rusty, Gable.
Oh, fudge.
♪ I believe in miracles ♪
♪ Where're you from? ♪
♪ You sexy thing... ♪
Frontier Realty. I
want a home for you.
No, the house is two
stories. We can't remove one.
Thanks.
♪ Where're you from... ♪
- Hi.
- Hey.
You all good, buddy?
I'm in the middle of
a high-intensity yoga.
Can you give me a minute?
Yeah, of course.
Listen to me.
Tell Knuckles I don't
know where she is.
Okay?
Not okay.
♪ You sexy thing ♪
♪ You sexy thing, you ♪
♪ I believe in miracles ♪
♪ Since you came along... ♪
Gable! Just the man
I'm looking for.
Goddamn, son, you
have looked better.
Come on in my office.
I want to talk at you.
You have won the Regional
Realtor of the Year!
You did it!
Congratulations.
I wanted to come down
and tell you myself.
I know how hard you've
been busting your tail.
Cliff.
Man, you come a long way.
Proud of you.
Uh... thank you.
This is, um...
This means a lot to me.
I'm overwhelmed.
When we first met,
you were a man adrift.
Now look at you.
I mean, you just keep
getting after it.
Marvin?
Sorry. Uh...
Can I borrow your car?
My bike, it-it's not working.
Hell, sure.
It's yours.
Whoa! We're hugging.
We're hugging.
You've taught me so much, Cliff.
I just want you to know that.
You've been a great mentor.
You changed my life.
Marvin, you can't change a man
who doesn't want to be changed.
I'll grab the car later.
"Crazy for you," my ass.
Man, what got your
panties in a bunch?
Is-is he ever gonna
move? Been there all day.
Man, how wifey doing?
What y'all got planned
for, uh, Valentine's Day?
She, um, kicked me out again.
Man, get the fuck off the block.
- Is you serious?
- Yeah.
Damn.
She said that I'm
emotionally constipated.
"Love bug."
That's what she used
to call me, all right?
Yeah, whatever.
Fucking love bug.
Look, maybe you should call her
and apologize for being so...
being so constipated, you know?
Yeah, maybe you should, maybe
you should eat my whole ass.
Maybe I should beat
your whole ass.
Yeah, maybe you
should try to do that.
- You know...
- What, motherfucker?
That's... that's what I
might fucking actually do.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
Is that him?
What?
-KING: Ay-yo, Merlo.
That boy Gable on
the move finally.
Well, that's weird, man.
He's probably going
to meet up with Rose.
All right?
Follow him and
find fucking Rose.
And you know what to do.
I'll keep Knuckles in the dark.
Fucking valentines!
Knuckles?
Am I interrupting, sir?
The Raven's not
answering his phone.
The Raven?
Wait, i-is this about
the valentines cards?
Yes.
It's Rose's handwriting, okay?
That I know.
About fucking time.
That's why I sent The Raven.
I thought we agreed to handle
the Rose situation in-house.
- Mmm.
- So why hire The Raven, too?
Now, the money that she
stole has been recovered.
She was a hell of a lawyer
for the organization.
Now she's just a-a loose end.
And we sure as hell
don't need The Raven...
If she's alive and back, she
could fuck everything up.
She knows whose money
that really was.
She's fucking with us right now.
All these goddamn
valentine cards.
Her idea of a game.
I need to find out why
Marvin didn't kill her
and decide if I'm
gonna kill her again.
Decide?
I mean, she stole from you.
We shouldn't hesitate
to kill her on sight.
Enough!
I said I want her alive.
Happy motherfucking
Valentine's Day.
Looks like love is...
Marvin Gable.
Yeah.
- Who are you?
- That's King, and I'm Otis.
Yeah, we work with your brother
and his right-hand
man, Renny Merlo.
They brought us in after your
little, uh, career change.
Damn, I thought your ass would
be a little more scarier.
But look, your place
here, it inspires me.
If a has-been killer like
yourself can, you know,
score a sweet little
civilian life like this,
maybe there's hope for me and O.
What you think? You
think I got a shot at it?
Anything's possible.
- How's your credit?
- My credit? Hmm?
Ha ha, ha ha.
- A little funny guy, huh?
- Fun.
Now, look, you bleeding
just a little bit too much
for a motherfucker who
don't know nothing.
And I think that you've
packed a little too much
for a guy who
isn't running away.
- Mm. Where you going, my boy?
- Okay?
Time to listen, little man.
- Listen!
- Listen, motherfucker.
- Yeah.
- Listen.
Where is Rose?
I don't know.
Come on, now.
You should've just told
us what we need to know.
Where is Rose, and why
did you not kill her?
- What are you doing?
- Hmm?
What are you doing?
I just opened that.
So what? It's fucking soda.
You-you trippin'. Fuck,
I thought we could share.
- C-Could you ask?
- Fuck, O, please forgive me.
Of course we can share.
Fuck!
Fuck that!
I'm on him.
I got it. I got it.
Get your ass over here.
- Yeah!
- Yeah, come here!
Damn, O!
Watch this, watch this.
Motherfucker!
- Tag team!
- Ah, no.
Your turn, your turn,
your turn, your turn.
Get him, O! Get him, O!
Fuck! Why?!
- Come here.
- Fuck him up, O.
Oh, shit!
Where you think you're
going? Oh, fuck!
What the fuck?!
- Motherfucker!
- Get the fuck in the fridge!
- Get your ass in there.
- Damn!
Bye!
Watch this, O. Watch this, O.
Shit, I missed!
Get him, O! Fuck him up!
Come on, come on.
Ooh, shit! Oh!
Okay. Okay.
Yeah. Don't think you're
so fucking cool now...
Hey! Where Rose at,
you little fuck?!
What...
Hey, that could've
been your head.
Tell my brother to back off.
I'm not telling
your brother shit!
You know what? I'm-a
kill your little ass.
What the...
How the fuck can I get this?
It's really stuck.
This little motherfucking
spider monkey ninja.
God!
Hey, Marv.
Rose?
Hey!
What the fuck is you...
See you tomorrow.
Hello?
Hey.
Do you happen to have an
appointment with Mr. Gable?
Mr. Knuckle. I am
not answering that.
"My blades are quiet,
sharp and clean.
"They cut through life unseen.
"No echo follows,
no scream, no cry.
Just steel and
flesh as I pass by."
Did you find her?
Man, we just got the
shit beat out of us.
- Marvin and Rose got away.
- Fuck!
This is so fucked up. Seriously.
-Fuck!
This motherfucker just
a little bit too crazy,
and me and O ain't
sign up for this shit.
K-King, listen to me
very carefully. Okay?
If she is taken alive, she
will tell Knuckles everything,
that Kippy fixed the books
and I stole the fucking money,
and we're all dead.
You guys are idiots.
I will find Rose myself
and fucking kill her.
And I'll text you the address
so you can clean up
what is left of her.
Okay? Oh.
And find Kippy, okay?
I mean, he hasn't been
returning my calls,
and that bastard
knows everything.
- And the fucker talks too much.
- All right, man. Fuck.
You all right, my boy?
No.
What am I wearing?
Hi! You've reached Marvin Gable
at Frontier Realty.
So sorry I missed your
call, but leave a message
and I'll get back to
you as soon as I can.
I want a home for you.
Hey. It's...
It's me. Um...
There's a dead poet
in your office.
Maybe you know that.
Maybe you don't.
Very funny, Rose.
I need you to hear
one of his poems.
It's called...
"The Dancing Bear."
"My dancing bear,
"sometimes prancing bear.
"So silent, so graceful.
"Do you have any wisdom for me,
"as you sway so charmingly
"inside your cage?
"Upon your stage, you move.
"Out here, the chains are thick.
"Out here, the
ringmaster's sick.
Those gray bars in your way
are so ill-fitting, so..."
I always had a sense
that Rose might
try to come back.
She had the guts to
stand up to anyone.
Even my brother Knuckles.
He tried to kill her once.
But I interfered
because I love her.
Even though she would never
look twice at a guy like me.
Oh. He does look
cute in that sweater.
I mean, look at him.
He's kind, he's
smart, he is a badass.
But he has to face his past
so we can get our lives back.
Consider this my
resignation, Marv.
I just can't dance anymore.
No one's ever...
...understood my words before.
Oh.
No one's words
have ever understood
me... before.
Hey, Andi, you got the bar?
Aw.
Well, I really hate
that you shaved.
You were the one...
The glasses are a nice touch.
Very Clark Kent.
I got you out.
What do you want, Rose?
A secured outcome
no matter the cost.
Exactly what outcome?
I want my life back, and
I need you to help me.
That's all.
Your life back? Why now?
Well, why not? It's
Valentine's Day.
I sent the whole gang
these cute little cards.
I learned calligraphy
and everything.
Do you think this is a joke?
We're in danger.
Okay, relax.
This isn't Knuckles' territory.
You are safe. We are safe.
We're not safe anywhere.
Do you have any idea
what you have done?
You need to run. Tonight.
Oh, because that's how you
deal with Knuckles, right?
"Running away."
I know exactly what I've done.
And I know exactly
what I'm doing.
Goodbye, Rose.
Marvin, this is it.
It's now... or never.
And I need your help.
Hey, hey, hey. I know you.
- Excuse me.
- No, it's you.
Your ads, man.
Your fucking bench ads.
I see your face everywhere I go!
-I'm so sorry.
What the fuck are you doing?
-Sorry, everyone.
I'll give you a ride.
Uh, Andi, can you
give Reggie some ice?
I was pleasantly surprised
to find this in your pocket.
Amethyst.
One of the best protections
against nightmares.
I'm the one who gave it to you.
Why'd you keep it?
I'm the sentimental type.
I know.
I love that about you.
Come on. Let's go.
What was that?
What? You are being paranoid.
You saved my award.
Well, yeah. I could barely
pry it out of your hands.
Slow down, could you?
Well, the Marvin I
know likes to go fast.
Oops.
- Rose?
- Mm-hmm?
What the heck are you doing?
I want to see the
real you, right now.
This is the real me.
The other guy's gone.
I buried him out in
the quarry with you.
No, no, no. I saw you
in the bar, babes.
You wanted to hurt that guy.
Marvin, come out!
- Please stop! Please stop!
- Come out wherever you are!
Fucking stop!
There he is.
"The fear I feel has
little to do with death,
"for we all die,
and everything to
do with not living."
Your observations?
You...
write about death a lot, um...
and killing.
It's who I am.
It's what I know.
Am I in danger?
From me?
No.
I'm the one in danger.
Of what?
♪ All the gold in the world,
no, it don't mean much... ♪
Falling.
♪ All the shine of the crown
might be good for looking ♪
♪ But when it all breaks down ♪
♪ Oh, they ain't got
nothing on you... ♪
It's one of my listings.
Hope to sell it this week.
♪ Like a lake down south
where we all hang out ♪
♪ With the Texas barbecue ♪
♪ Like the sound of a song... ♪
Pull into the garage.
♪ Laying down some
two-chord truth... ♪
Yeah. Let's do this shit.
Rose.
I like it here.
Feels good.
It's got a great layout,
lots of space, good light.
- What?
- Nothing.
You're cute.
There are rooms upstairs
if you're tired.
What's your whole deal
with this thing anyway?
After I left Knuckles,
I honestly didn't think
I could be normal.
This proves I can.
I've changed, Rose.
Mm.
No, you haven't.
You're just hiding.
What are you doing,
Rose? Are you crazy?
I didn't come here to hide.
Hey, I worked hard
to get to where I am.
And because of you, I lost
everything in one day.
Oh, I know exactly how
that feels, Marvin.
Exactly.
Why couldn't you
just stay dead, Rose?
Because it's humiliating.
No name, no truth.
You got nothing.
You're nobody.
I'm nobody.
Hiding ain't living.
But if you want to
live to see next week,
you'll run far away and
never show your face again.
Well, I already did that.
Now I'm trying
something different.
How far would you go
to get your life back?
I already did.
Follow me. I got to
show you something.
"Look in the mirror, fuckface."
Kippy.
Why is Knuckles'
accountant in your trunk?
It's all part of the plan.
And where is his finger?
Marvin, you are not listening.
I told you I want my life back,
and I'll do what
it fucking takes.
Cutting off his finger, Rose?
Do you realize what a
dangerous game you're playing?
Look, I needed a fingerprint.
Yes, I know.
Look at that.
It's his dental caps.
I'll be needing those back.
Hello, Marv.
All right.
Now I want to know
what you and Merlo got
out of setting me up.
Three years ago, I helped Merlo
steal four million dollars.
Of that sweet Russian money.
Money you...
...were going to hide
by cooking the books
so Knuckles would never miss it.
Which, by the way, he didn't,
because you fools put it
in the trunk of my
car for him to find.
Now, I'm a smart girl.
I can think of a few reasons
why you'd want me
out of the picture.
But why, why, why
risk being killed
stealing money from Knuckles
just to give it all back to him?
Now, that just
doesn't make sense.
That's easy.
We had no intention
of keeping the money.
Merlo wanted your position
as Knuckles' right hand.
Oh.
He was willing to risk it all,
and the two million dollars in
the, in the boot of your car,
well, that was enough to
put you six feet under.
You said "two million."
We stole four.
So, pray tell,
where's the other two?
Don't waste my time, Kippy. You
want to lose another finger?
Okay, okay.
Merlo has it.
He paid me for fixing the
books and took the rest.
Fucking Merlo.
He set me up.
Mm. Yeah, I think so, yeah.
Framed me and kept the other
two million for himself.
So, Marv.
You did drive me to a quarry
and leave me for dead.
I made Knuckles a fortune
laundering money
from the Russians,
- but as you know, I wanted out.
- Marvin?
Stealing money with Merlo
was never a good idea.
You don't have to do this.
We can still... Whoa!
Of course that
motherfucker framed me.
Rose Carlisle is dead.
Don't come back.
The rule of the company is:
If you steal from
Knuckles, you die.
But you broke that rule.
Marv.
- And defied your brother.
- No.
And I'm so grateful.
But I just got to ask:
Did you know they
were setting me up?
I didn't know, okay?
You didn't know?
You didn't know?!
I knew you were a thief,
I knew you were a liar,
and I knew my brother
wanted you dead.
Oh, so you just
volunteered for the job?
Yeah.
Listen.
If I didn't do it,
someone else would have.
You'd be gone.
And I knew if I took the job,
it was the only chance
I had to save you.
I didn't want to imagine
a world without you.
The Russians.
She knows it all.
Valentine's Day, right?
It's not my fucking day.
Motherfucker took a swing at me.
Yeah.
Uh, what the fuck is that?
Got it for Cindy
for Valentine's.
That's why we made
this fucking stop?
Bruh, it's simple.
Ain't no fake-ass,
made-in-Sri-Lanka teddy bear
gon' help you get your
fucking wife back.
Get your fucking mind
together, my boy.
Oh.
Give the motherfucker his
bear back, and let's go.
We got to go clean
up after Merlo.
Marvin?
What in the hell?
Marvin, you here?
I'm here to pick up the car.
Your front door's wide open.
Oh, uh...
Hi.
I'm Alvin.
My friends call me Knuckles.
Cliff Cussick. Howdy.
Ah. My brother's savior.
You're the one he spends
Thanksgiving with now, right?
Yeah.
Yeah, Marvin comes
over at Thanksgiving.
He's family.
I'm sorry. You
have to forgive me.
I'm a little, uh, surprised.
Marvin never mentioned
that he had a... brother.
Drink?
Oh.
You're not gonna have one?
I still got a little bit left.
No, thank you, kindly.
Where-where is he?
I mean, I haven't seen
Marvin since he left work,
and he wasn't looking too good.
- What a considerate boss.
- Yeah.
He's family, I told
you. He's my brother.
I got to be honest
with you, Cliff.
It hurts my feelings that
Marvin never mentioned me.
Oh, well, maybe he did.
My memory's not
like it used to be.
You want to feel better?
Marvin never told me
he played baseball.
Oh, I can assure you, Cliff,
there's a lot Marvin
didn't tell you.
Rose is right.
I am hiding.
I allowed my brother to turn me
into someone I
never wanted to be.
I could take you to at least a
dozen holes in the old quarry
that Marvin filled with bodies.
He was such a...
beautiful, beautiful monster.
But I controlled it.
He was obedient, did
what I said, always.
And when I unleashed him...
Oh.
I could take you
to the last hole.
But all you'd find is a hole.
'Cause apparently, he fell in
love and found a conscience.
Ever see her around?
No, sir, I don't believe I have.
You sure?
She seems like the kind of
woman a man would remember.
I don't know if
Marvin understands
I'm here to save him.
Just like he saved me.
We have to face Knuckles
to be truly free, and...
I don't want to
do it without him.
Goddamn, Alvin.
Those are some big words.
I got to be honest. I, uh...
I don't know that much about
the world you're talking about.
But I'm not naive enough to know
there's gonna be anything I
can say in this room right now
that's gonna change my fate.
I'll tell you what.
I believe in absolution.
I believe in second chances.
The difference between
putting bodies in holes
and families in homes...
...is pretty big.
Maybe too big.
Knuckles only set me free
because I promised to kill Rose.
Now he will never
stop hunting us.
I know I have to face my
past to be truly free.
But goddamn it,
I love this new life.
From the minute he started
selling homes for me,
he was working like he was
making up for something.
You know what?
Think I will take that drink.
And when push comes to shove,
Marvin's gonna be all right.
You're a wise man, Cliff.
But...
Marvin only has one brother.
Oh.
Morning, Marv.
- Painkillers.
- Oh.
Mm-hmm.
Oh, yeah.
I appreciate that.
I got to say,
a lot of intrigue with
this whole money situation.
Proper fucking quagmire.
Merlo and I thought
we were real smart
when we set up Rose
the way we did.
Knuckles still doesn't know
we stole more than what
he found in Rose's trunk.
But you know the rule:
If you steal from
Knuckles, you die.
Fuck me, man.
I would not like to be you
when your brother
finds out Rose is here.
Finds out?
Not that he will.
I mean, I won't say anything.
No.
But I tell you what.
A little bit of hush money
might just put both
of our minds at ease.
Why are you shutting the doors?
You know what I used to
do for my brother, right?
My job.
Yeah, of course. Everyone knew.
But you don't do that anymore.
Well, Kippy, you're not
giving me much of a choice.
Oh, fuck.
It's the Reebers.
Marvin?
Don't open that door.
Please. I love this life.
Hiding ain't living.
- Morning, Marvin!
- Oh, morning, Marvin!
- Chet, Sherry, good morning.
- Hi. -CHET: Oh, my goodness.
What happened to your hand there, buddy?
-
Uh, I'm fine. Bike accident.
Have you made a decision?
Well, we thought
about it, and...
- Here, hold my hand.
- Of course.
We want this home from you!
- Living room.
- Living room. Okay, great.
Oh. Every time.
It's so welcoming.
"[playing quietly]
Marv.
It's me.
Yeah, I know. Uh, where are you?
What is going on? Are you okay?
I'm fine. Listen.
Um, did you, did
you get my message?
No. Why?
Um, I just... I quit, is all.
Again?
- I'm not happy.
- Marvin, look. It's you!
I need a change, Marv.
Can you quit later?
I need you to
bring me the papers
to the Emerald Springs house.
R-Right now?
Yes, right now.
The Reebers are here,
and they want to buy.
Yeah. Um, I just...
I don't think that I should.
Ashley, it's important.
Fine. Fine, fine,
fine, fine, fine.
Fine, fine, fine, fuck, fuck.
- Where is he?
- Shit!
Chet?
Are these the new
energy efficient models?
Uh...
Yes.
Aren't they great?
They're gorgeous.
They're perfect.
You know what?
I'm just not sold on this chair.
I found your brother.
Is Rose with him?
I don't know. I'm on my way.
Be as hard on him
as you need to be,
but I want them both alive.
I... I need you to stay.
Forever.
If it were that easy.
Please. Stay here with me.
I know that out there
is all the-the death
and the killing that
you write about,
but in here, you can be
who I know you really are.
And we can be whatever
we want to be.
We-we... we can be
poets, we can be artists,
we can be creators.
I don't have a choice.
Fine, neither do I.
So I am...
I'm coming with you.
Hold... Stop walking fast.
What do you want?
Hey, boss. How you doing?
Just get back to LKP.
I need someone there
when The Raven shows up.
He found Marvin and maybe Rose.
Okay, okay.
Why don't I just call The Raven,
and I'll get the
details myself...
Did I fucking stutter?!
The Raven already did your job.
But listen...
Hey!
Back away from the car!
That's my car!
Who's this?
It's Kippy!
Kippy! What the fuck
is going on, man?!
I know where the
bloodthirsty bitch is.
They are both in
Emerald Springs.
Thank you.
I got to get the
fuck out of here.
Ah, fuck!
Marvin motherfucking Gable.
Goddamn.
Talk to me, man.
Honey, where's my money?
Well, well, well, Rose.
My funny valentine.
You get my message, you
stupid piece of shit?
Spell it out clear
enough for you?
Nice detective work.
I didn't know you
understood Russian.
Let me ask you this
one question, though.
Do you want your fucking money?
Hmm?
Come to LKP.
Come if you dare, bitch.
I just need a moment to think.
As soon as Ashley gets here,
I'll get you
squared before I go.
- Rose.
- Go?
Wait, wait. Where
are you going, Marv?
What are you doing?
- A vacation.
- I've got to help Rose.
A long vacation.
-SHERRY: You're running away, Marv?
- Can I?
- Don't leave us.
- We need you.
- Excuse me.
Where are you...?
Rose! Rose!
Everything okay, Marv?
Should we come back later or...?
No.
I want this home for you.
Marv, you better follow me.
- What we doing, boss?
- Forget about cleaning up, man.
Rose never showed.
Raven, on the other hand, that
motherfucker is flying his ass
all the way to Emerald
Springs to pick up Gable.
Now, I need you to beat
him there and kill Gable.
All right, and if Raven gets in
the way, kill him, too, okay?
Guy's a fucking weirdo.
I don't trust him.
What if Rose is with him?
- She's not gonna be.
- And what about Kippy?
She's not, all right?
Gentlemen, listen, listen.
It's time we tie up
loose ends... yeah?
We fuck off and we rebuild.
Raven and Gable?
How the fuck are
we gonna do that?
Firepower, man.
Lots and lots of
fucking firepower.
That'll be Ashley with the...
...paperwork.
Marv, really sorry.
It's just, your brother
wants to talk to you.
Um, he won't hurt you
as long as you come quietly.
And remember what we
talked about, Roger.
Roger?
Stop being scary.
- Oh.
- Well, hi.
- Hello.
Who's this?
This is, uh, an old colleague.
More of a rival, really.
A ri... a rival?
Wow, that's exciting.
Ashley, why don't
you take the Reebers
into the kitchen
and get started.
No.
It's okay.
Great.
Let's go to the kitchen.
Come on. Let's. This way.
Oh.
Come along.
Hello again, Mr. Gable.
Hey, it's Cindy.
Leave a message.
Hey, baby, it's me. Um...
King and I, we're about
to do something very dumb,
and I just wanted to call
you just in case, um,
you know, whatever.
Anyways, um, sorry
if I've been...
...aloof and
emotionally unavailable.
You deserve better.
I will be better, and I...
I belong by your side.
I just need to kill some people.
It's work. It's-it's work.
Miss you.
And that's all I wanted to say.
Thanks. Yeah.
That was lame.
Nah, bruh, that shit was real.
I'm proud of you, blood.
Why'd you park so far away?
-What?
I'll tell you what, that sunken
living room is a game changer.
Imagine the parties. Ooh-ooh!
Right?
- See you later.
- What the fuck?
You like walking around a
residential area with your...
- with fucking guns?
- Look, I just wanted
to stretch my legs a little bit.
-
Where is Rose Carlisle?
Gone.
- That's too bad.
- You read all this, right?
Okay.
Let's-let's discuss this later.
Let's Swiss-cheese
these motherfuckers.
I think the time has come.
To duck!
Whoo!
These guys work for Merlo!
They will kill us all!
So, same team?
Hmm.
Hello?
Go!
We brought firepower!
Marvin Gable, where
the fuck you at?
You take the fanny pack guy.
We don't want to hurt anyone.
We're just here to talk.
Huh? Where the fuck... Oh.
Feathers? Really?
Gable, bring your scary ass
from up over there, baby.
Man, who the fuck are you?
I'm a black belt, motherfucker.
Hey!
- Jeff?
- Marv.
Congratulations on the Regional
Realtor of the Year Award.
I was showing the
house next door.
Looked like you needed help.
- But they got guns.
- I know.
Sounds like a reload.
- You go low, I go high.
- No, Jeff!
No!
That was my bullet.
- No, that's my bullet.
- No, it was mine.
- It was mine.
- No, it was actually...
- Gable!
- Get that little motherfucker!
- Oh!
Damn!
Oh. Fucking psycho!
Bitch-ass Raven. Beastmode!
Here, take that.
- You guys...
- I need to find something sharp.
What the hell is going on?
Uh, everything's fine.
- Marv.
- No, no, no, no.
Chet, Sherry, how
are you holding up?
Not good, Marv.
Get on your fucking feet, Raven.
You're on the menu.
- Bon appétit.
- Fuck yeah.
I'm so sorry about this.
I'll get these guys out
of here as soon as I can
and get right back
to your paperwork.
Come on!
Think you're fucking invincible?
Who you think you
are, you fucking...
Yeah, you little
feather-throwing motherfucker.
I'm on your shit, boy.
Oh, shit!
Bitch, is you crazy?
St-Stop it!
Stay here and don't come
out until I come get you.
- Please.
- Okay. Okay, okay.
Marv, Marv.
And don't worry.
I've got guys who can patch
all of this up like new.
What?
Oh, Ashley. Are you okay?
MARVIN and THE RAVEN: Sorry.
Stop!
Stop it! Stop it, you two! Stop!
Stop! Stop, stop!
Marv, please don't kill him.
Ash, he's a bad man.
Stop! Bad?
For fuck's sake,
well, what are you?
What-what are any of us?
You told me to find something
that I love and to go after it.
And I have.
And it's him.
I should listen
to my own advice.
Zaks, thank you.
Merlo?
Where's my goddamn money?
Rose.
Rosie, Rosie, Rosie.
My fucking valentine.
You know, for a ghost,
you sure have been
stirring up some shit.
Only took a few swings to
knock the truth out of him.
You think you can play me? Steal my money?
-
She knows everything, boss.
But I was gonna stop her.
Shut the fuck up!
You're already a dead man.
- Yes, sir.
- You, Merlo and Kippy.
So, what was the plan?
- Start over?
- Mm.
It doesn't work that way, Rosie.
You steal from me, you die.
Boss, listen, she's got
access to all the accounts.
Welcome home, Marv.
Want a boba?
Look at you, Marv.
You're a mess.
See, this is what happens
when you go off on your own.
I knew you'd come.
I need you, Marv.
I need all of you.
The good, the bad,
the everything.
Knight in fucking shining
armor, aren't you, brother?
There he is.
My monster.
Cut him down. Everyone.
It's about fucking time.
♪ The first, my last ♪
♪ My everything ♪
♪ And the answer to ♪
♪ All my dreams ♪
♪ You're my sun, my moon ♪
♪ My guiding star ♪
♪ My kind of wonderful ♪
♪ That's what you are ♪
♪ I know there's only ♪
♪ Only one like you ♪
♪ There's no way ♪
♪ They could have made two ♪
Mmm.
♪ You're-you're all
I'm living for ♪ -
♪ Your love, I'll
keep forevermore ♪
♪ You're the first,
you're the last ♪
♪ My everything ♪
♪ In you ♪
♪ I found ♪
♪ So many things ♪
♪ A love so new ♪
♪ Only you could bring ♪
♪ Can't you see it's you? ♪
♪ You make me feel this way ♪
♪ You're like a
first morning dew ♪
♪ On a brand-new day ♪
♪ I see ♪
♪ So many ways that I ♪
♪ Can love you till ♪
♪ The day I die ♪
♪ You're my reality ♪
♪ Yet I'm lost in a dream ♪
♪ You're the first, the last ♪
♪ My everything ♪
♪ You're my sun ♪
♪ My moon ♪
♪ My guiding star ♪
♪ My kind of wonderful ♪
Oh, I'm gonna enjoy this, bitch.
♪ That's what you are ♪
♪ I know ♪
♪ There's only ♪
♪ Only one like you ♪
♪ There's no way... ♪
Never forget, dear brother,
you've never beaten
me in a fight.
Not once.
And after you lose today,
this will again be your home.
Like my hat?
Cliff seemed like a good guy.
But he was never your brother.
I'm your brother.
Brother?
No brother would
use me like you did.
We're a team.
I hate seeing you
like this, Marv.
You belong with me now.
With you?
Never again.
All you had to do was kill Rose.
Goodbye, Alvin.
Rose, it's me.
Merlo was right.
I do know everything.
Huh?
What did you do?
Well, I hand-delivered
one last special
Valentine's Day card.
Along with a small gift.
A finger.
More specifically, a fingerprint
belonging to our favorite
Kiwi pal and accountant...
...granting access to
your personal finances.
Which is proof
you've been skimming
from our oh-so-serious
Russki suppliers for years.
- Za zdorovie.
I was able to broker a
pretty lucrative deal.
Great plan, right?
My finder's fee.
Do you have any
idea what you've...
Marvin. Marvin!
Brother, please.
Don't let Rose ruin everything.
Happy Valentine's, dickhead.
Rose! Rose!
- Please wait.
- We did it, Marv.
Now go back to the
life you love so much.
Rose, there's something
I have to tell you.
What? What do you
need to tell me?
I love you.
I always have.
Well, say it again.
Make me believe it.
It's like I said.
Valentine's Day is filled
with the unexpected.
You're dangerous.
Whether it's finding new love...
What's Cindy want?
It worked.
...or the opportunity
for second chances...
I told you, motherfucker.
My boy.
♪ The things we do for love ♪
♪ Communication is... ♪
...or even just
giving us the reason
to express the true love
that has always been there.
♪ The weather's turned and... ♪
As much as love hurts,
it's totally worth it.
♪ Like walking in the
rain and the snow ♪
♪ When there's nowhere to go ♪
♪ And you're feeling like
a part of you is dying ♪
♪ And you're looking for
the answer in her eyes ♪
♪ You think you're
gonna break up ♪
♪ Then she says she
wants to make up ♪
♪ Ooh, you made me love you ♪
♪ Ooh, you've got a way ♪
♪ Ooh, you had me crawling ♪
♪ Up the wall ♪
♪ Like walking in the
rain and the snow ♪
♪ When there's nowhere to go ♪
♪ And you're feeling like
a part of you is dying ♪
♪ And you're looking for
the answer in her eyes ♪
♪ You think you're
gonna break up ♪
♪ Then she says she
wants to make up ♪
♪ Ooh, you made me love you ♪
♪ Ooh, you've got a way ♪
♪ Ooh, you had me crawling ♪
♪ Up the wall ♪
♪ A compromise would
surely help the situation ♪
♪ Agree to disagree
but disagree to part ♪
♪ When after all it's
just a compromise of ♪
♪ The things we do for love ♪
♪ The things we
do for love... ♪